{
  "arc_name": "Arlong Park",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What object does Genzo have on his hat?",
      "answer": "A pinwheel"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was Nami caught stealing from her village as a child?",
      "answer": "Books. Charting/navigation books"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did the Arlong pirates spot Bellemere’s house?",
      "answer": "Smoke from cooking"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the Arlong Pirates want Nami?",
      "answer": "The maps she drew"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who sent the marines to find Nami’s money?",
      "answer": "Arlong"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who prevented the villagers from rushing into Arlong park just to die?",
      "answer": "Johnny and Yosaku"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does Luffy get his feet stuck in the ground while fighting Arlong?",
      "answer": "He stomped the ground too hard"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does Arlong take Luffy out of the fight almost immediately?",
      "answer": "Picking him up and throwing him into the sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many swords does Hachi use?",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do Genzo and Nojiko get Luffy air while he is trapped?",
      "answer": "They stretch his neck"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did Sanji stun Kuroobi long enough to prevent himself from drowning?",
      "answer": "Forced air into his gills"
    }
  ]
}
